[Subtitles by danielsangeo]
All right. I've figured it out.
You guys are zombies.
Not the horror movie kind, but
the honest-to-God voodoo kind.
Somebody resurrected you from the dead
and he's on his lunch break or something
so that's why you're just standing here
next to all these lasers and guns.
I can't help you guys because your brains
are being controlled by somebody else.
Oh, yeah, see, there's your
master up there.
I should go talk to him. Maybe I
can buy one of you off him.
You could help out around the
house or something.
Besides, I have a gun.
Everything's for sale when you have a gun.
I know how to talk to these
people; I've been to Haiti.
Les yeux de Dieu
ne regardent pas beaucoup là.
Hey, is that some more ammo?
All right! High-five!
Well... forget it.
I am a little envious of those
guys, actually;
just standing there next to
things that could kill them.
I wish I could be like that.
Just not care whether I live or die.
Considering every retarded risk
I've taken this morning,
you'd think I don't care, but I do.
I don't want to die.
I want other people to die FOR me.
SCIENTIST: Rescued at last!
Thank GOD you're here!
Ah, the rescue team!
[machine gun fire]
Or, um... what?
Okay, I can understand shooting
someone running at you screaming, but...
I dunno, this feels shady.
Is there another way out of here?
I think this guy's in a bad mood.
No... all right, fine.
I'll try and go make friends,
even though that always
ends up the same way.
See, he's not even trying to
plant a gun on him or hide the body.
That's a bad sign. Like this is
just another day at work for him.
I'll at least give him some
warning so I don't sneak up on him.
HECU: Maintain lookout.
This guy's jumpy.
Hey, killer. What's up?
[machine gun fire]
God! Jesus! Shit...
Dammit.
Diplomacy sucks!
[machine gun fire]
OW!
Man, what's your problem?!
And why are you shooting everyone?!
I'm taking this gun away
from you, mister.
You're obviously not mature
enough to handle it.
Now, you sit there and think
about what you've done.
Somebody needs to explain what
the term "rescue" means to that guy.
It does NOT mean whatever
he thinks it means.
Well, more ammo.
I wish I could save all this for
a rainy day, but the way this day's going,
it must be pouring outside right now.
Not that I'd know anything about that;
I'm still stuck in these catacombs.
So, yeah, guess I just killed a guy.
Totally on purpose this time.
I'll just keep on moving and not
really think about that.
SCIENTIST: Don't kill me! I'm
with the Science Team!
Hey, me too, but you go on first
just in case they're not cool with that.
[machine gun fire]
Yeah, see, I'm just getting
some bad vibes here.
Is there another floor I can get off on?
I think this is the wrong one.
No...
Well, maybe I'm being a pessimist,
but I just don't think I'm going
to get along with these guys.
It's like a throwback to high school where
everyone had their--oh, more ammo--
where everyone had their own cliques and you
had to watch what you said to which group.
I guess the difference is here
there won't be so much drama.
We all have guns so we should be
able to work out our differences pretty quickly,
and won't have to draw this out
over the school year.
CUT IT OUT!
SEE, YOU GUYS PROBABLY NEVER GOT
OVER THIS CRAP FROM HIGH SCHOOL!
I WENT ON TO COLLEGE!
OW!
I HAVE A DOCTOR'S DEGREE!
You guys are dicks!
I know what's going on here.
Every one of you wants to be the
big hero for rescuing us
but you can't decide so you
fight over it.
Instead of taking turns, you just shoot
anyone who walks out the door
so that no one else can take
credit for the rescue.
God damn!
Congratulations!
You won the prize!
You're all dead.
Yuck...
So, how many people have I
killed now? Three or four?
I think that one guy killed his buddy with
a grenade, which doesn't surprise me at all.
Okay, left... right...
I'll go this way, I'll just
crawl this time.
Save my back.
I still don't even know what
any of these lasers do,
just that it's probably not good.
I don't think these are like those
coupon dispensers at the grocery store.
Man, I don't think I want to go
this way; I'm just going to turn around.
So, yeah. I'm killing people now.
But that was NOT murder. That
was TOTALLY self-defense.
Just because I had a submachine
gun doesn't change anything.
It just lets me defend more efficiently.
I haven't murdered anyone.
Err, not today, anyway.
All right, where am I going?
I think I did a U-turn again;
this looks like a dead end.
There's no steps, of course.
Well this conveyor might go
somewhere, but it's going the wrong way.
Yeah, I don't wanna--WHOA!
Okay, fuck this. There's gotta
be another way out of here.
Oh, hey, I can just climb up there.
Okay...
HECU: No sign objective, sir.
Oh no.
So, we going to play nice, or...?
HECU: Movement! Shit!
Nope.
Well, looks like my armor's
better than yours.
And I'll just loot your bodies
because that's how I roll.
And that puts me at six or seven
counts of self defense.
All right.
Heeeeyyyyy!  "Surface Access"!
Yes!
Score!
[exhale]
Y'know, I think murder used to be
legal in Texas, if it was in your house
and your wife was having sex
with another man.
Hm, maybe you had to be drunk, too.
They have drive-through
beer stands in Texas.